Guide to the Ron Kolm Papers, 1970-2016 MSS.079
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Accretions 2000-2001 - Series VI: Announcements
  - Subseries A: Readings
    - Brooklyn Lyceum, undated (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - Buhl's Loft, undated (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - By Herself: Women Reclaim Poetry, undated (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - CBGB, undated (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - CCS Reading Series, undated (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - Cedar Tavern, undated (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - Charas Community Center, undated (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - Chelsea Lounge, undated (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - Chez LaRoe, undated (Box 23, Folder 53)
    - Chico West Garden, undated (Box 23, Folder 54)
    - China Club, undated (Box 23, Folder 55)
    - Clovis Press, undated (Box 23, Folder 56)
    - Cornelia Street Cafunittitle>, undated (Box 23, Folder 57)
    - Consulate General of France, undated (Box 23, Folder 58)
    - Den of Sin, undated (Box 23, Folder 59)
    - DIA Center for the Arts, undated (Box 23, Folder 60)
    - Dixon Place, undated (Box 23, Folder 61)
    - First Unitarian Church, undated (Box 23, Folder 62)
    - Frank's Lounge, undated (Box 23, Folder 63)
    - Galapagos, undated (Box 23, Folder 64)
    - Gathering of the Tribes, undated (Box 23, Folder 65)
    - Gershwin Hotel, undated (Box 23, Folder 66)
    - Good World Bar and Bar, undated (Box 23, Folder 67)
    - Greenwich Village Bistro, undated (Box 23, Folder 68)
    - Groove, undated (Box 23, Folder 69)
    - Housing Works, undated (Box 23, Folder 70)
    - Internet Cafunittitle>, undated (Box 23, Folder 71)
    - Joe's Pub, undated (Box 23, Folder 72)
    - KGB Bar, undated (Box 23, Folder 73)
    - Knitting Factory, undated (Box 23, Folder 74)
    - La Perla Garden, undated (Box 23, Folder 75)
    - Locus Media, undated (Box 23, Folder 76)
    - Lungfull!, undated (Box 23, Folder 77)
    - Lida, David, undated (Box 23, Folder 78)
    - Life, undated (Box 23, Folder 79)
    - Little Theater, undated (Box 23, Folder 80)
    - Living Room, undated (Box 23, Folder 81)
    - Lotus Center, undated (Box 23, Folder 82)
    - Lower East Side Festival, undated (Box 23, Folder 83)
    - Lower East Side Tenement Museum, undated (Box 23, Folder 84)
    - Mamma Cassie's Coffee Shop, undated (Box 23, Folder 85)
    - Mid-Manhattan Library, undated (Box 23, Folder 86)
    - Moroccan Star, undated (Box 23, Folder 87)
    - Museum of the City of New York, undated (Box 23, Folder 88)
    - Myles, Eileen, undated (Box 23, Folder 89)
    - New York Performance Works, undated (Box 23, Folder 90)
    - New York Press, undated (Box 23, Folder 91)
    - Nuyorican Poets' Cafe, undated (Box 23, Folder 92)
    - Ohm, undated (Box 23, Folder 93)
    - Parkside Lounge, undated (Box 23, Folder 94)
    - Poets and Writers, undated (Box 23, Folder 95)
    - Poets House, undated (Box 23, Folder 96)
    - Poet to Poet, undated (Box 23, Folder 97)
    - Reading Between A and B, undated (Box 23, Folder 98)
    - Reading Room, undated (Box 23, Folder 99)
    - Rightbank Cafe, undated (Box 23, Folder 100)
    - Schein, Lorraine, undated (Box 23, Folder 101)
    - Segue Space, undated (Box 23, Folder 102)
    - Seven Stories Press, undated (Box 23, Folder 103)
    - Sideshow, undated (Box 23, Folder 104)
    - S. J. South Bar, undated (Box 23, Folder 105)
    - Skanky Possum Press, undated (Box 23, Folder 106)
    - Slaymakers, Bob, undated (Box 23, Folder 107)
    - Spa, undated (Box 23, Folder 108)
    - Splendid Bar and Cafe, undated (Box 23, Folder 109)
    - Stalke Galleri, undated (Box 23, Folder 110)
    - State of Art Gallery, undated (Box 23, Folder 111)
    - St. Mark's Church, undated (Box 23, Folder 112)
    - Teachers & Writers Collaborative, undated (Box 23, Folder 113)
    - Temple Bar, undated (Box 23, Folder 114)
    - Thread Waxing Space, undated (Box 23, Folder 115)
    - Tomkiw, Lydia, undated (Box 23, Folder 116)
    - Tower Books, undated (Box 23, Folder 117)
    - Tribes Gallery, undated (Box 23, Folder 118)
    - Two Girls, undated (Box 23, Folder 119)
    - Yakity Yak, undated (Box 23, Folder 120)
    - Zinc Bar, undated (Box 23, Folder 121)
  - Subseries B: Gallery Show Announcements
    - 304 Art, undated (Box 23, Folder 122)
    - ABC No Rio, undated (Box 23, Folder 123)
    - A.I.R. Gallery, undated (Box 23, Folder 124)
    - Alliance for the Arts, undated (Box 23, Folder 125)
    - Art Resources Transfer Inc., undated (Box 23, Folder 126)
    - Beaver Group, undated (Box 23, Folder 127)
    - Berenberg Gallery, undated (Box 23, Folder 128)
    - Bluestockings, undated (Box 23, Folder 129)
    - Brooklyn Artist Bookmakers, undated (Box 23, Folder 130)
    - Bound & Unbound, undated (Box 23, Folder 131)
    - Brecht Forum, undated (Box 23, Folder 132)
    - Bronfman Center for Jewish Student Life, undated (Box 23, Folder 133)
    - Brooklyn Museum of Art, undated (Box 23, Folder 134)
    - Bruce Weber's No Chance Ensemble, undated (Box 23, Folder 135)
    - Bucknell Art Gallery, undated (Box 23, Folder 136)
    - Carbon, undated (Box 23, Folder 137)
    - CBGB's Gallery, undated (Box 23, Folder 138)
    - Century Center, undated (Box 23, Folder 139)
    - Cheetah, undated (Box 23, Folder 140)
    - Chez LaRoe, undated (Box 23, Folder 141)
    - China Club, undated (Box 23, Folder 142)
    - Church of St. Andrew, undated (Box 23, Folder 143)
    - Church, Tom, undated (Box 23, Folder 144)
    - Circus Amok, undated (Box 23, Folder 145)
    - Club Europa, undated (Box 23, Folder 146)
    - Cokkie Snoei, undated (Box 23, Folder 147)
    - Dobbin Books, undated (Box 23, Folder 148)
    - Collective Unconscious, undated (Box 23, Folder 149)
    - Cooler, undated (Box 23, Folder 150)
    - Cpop Gallery, undated (Box 23, Folder 151)
    - Cream, undated (Box 23, Folder 152)
    - Currican Theatre, undated (Box 23, Folder 153)
    - dfn Gallery, undated (Box 23, Folder 154)
    - Den of Sin, undated (Box 23, Folder 155)
    - Dia Center for the Arts, undated (Box 23, Folder 156)
    - Digitas, undated (Box 23, Folder 157)
    - Dixon Place, undated (Box 23, Folder 158)
    - Double Happiness, undated (Box 23, Folder 159)
    - Downtown Music Gallery, undated (Box 23, Folder 160)
    - Dumba, undated (Box 23, Folder 161)
    - Editions Fawbush, undated (Box 23, Folder 162)
    - Egizio's Project, undated (Box 23, Folder 163)
    - Exhibition Space 156, undated (Box 23, Folder 164)
    - Ezra and Cecile Zilkha Gallery, undated (Box 23, Folder 165)
    - Fad, undated (Box 23, Folder 166)
    - Film Forum, undated (Box 23, Folder 167)
    - Fleischer Art Memorial, undated (Box 23, Folder 168)
    - Fordham University Law Building, undated (Box 23, Folder 169)
    - Foundry Theatre, undated (Box 23, Folder 170)
    - Franklin Furnace Archive, Inc., undated (Box 23, Folder 171)
    - Frederieke Taylor, undated (Box 23, Folder 172)
    - Galapagos Performance Space, undated (Box 23, Folder 173)
    - Gallery@49, undated (Box 23, Folder 174)
    - Gathering of the Tribes Gallery, undated (Box 23, Folder 175)
    - Geoffrey Young Gallery, undated (Box 23, Folder 176)
    - Grady Alexis Gallery, undated (Box 23, Folder 177)
    - Granary Books, undated (Box 23, Folder 178)
    - Green Door, undated (Box 23, Folder 179)
    - Greene-Naftali Gallery, undated (Box 23, Folder 180)
    - Grey Art Gallery, undated (Box 23, Folder 181)
    - Grolier Club, undated (Box 23, Folder 182)
    - Guggenheim Museum, undated (Box 23, Folder 183)
    - Hallway, undated (Box 23, Folder 184)
    - Heffernan, Julie, undated (Box 23, Folder 185)
    - Holland Tunnel, undated (Box 23, Folder 186)
    - Jacob K. Javits Center, undated (Box 23, Folder 187)
    - Jane Street Theatre, undated (Box 23, Folder 188)
    - Jan van der Donk, undated (Box 23, Folder 189)
    - Jewish Museum, undated (Box 23, Folder 190)
    - Joe's Pub, undated (Box 23, Folder 191)
    - Key Club, undated (Box 23, Folder 192)
    - The Kitchen, undated (Box 23, Folder 193)
    - Kitsch Inn, undated (Box 23, Folder 194)
    - Knitting Factory, undated (Box 23, Folder 195)
    - La Mama, undated (Box 23, Folder 196)
    - Lark Theatre Company, undated (Box 23, Folder 197)
    - Le Bar Bat, undated (Box 23, Folder 198)
    - Life, undated (Box 23, Folder 199)
    - Life Cafe, undated (Box 23, Folder 200)
    - Lightworks, undated (Box 23, Folder 201)
    - Little Theater, undated (Box 23, Folder 202)
    - Lower East Side Festival, undated (Box 23, Folder 203)
    - Luna Lounge, undated (Box 23, Folder 204)
    - Marcel Sitcoske Gallery, undated (Box 23, Folder 205)
    - Margaret Bodell Gallery, undated (Box 23, Folder 206)
    - MASS MoCA, undated (Box 23, Folder 207)
    - McIntosh/Panich Gallery, undated (Box 23, Folder 208)
    - Medicine Show, undated (Box 23, Folder 209)
    - Merce Cunningham Dance Studio, undated (Box 23, Folder 210)
    - Metronome, undated (Box 23, Folder 211)
    - Meulener, Brian, undated (Box 23, Folder 212)
    - Millenium Film Workshop, undated (Box 23, Folder 213)
    - Mother, undated (Box 23, Folder 214)
    - MWF Video Club, undated (Box 23, Folder 215)
    - New Museum, undated (Box 23, Folder 216)
    - New World Grill, undated (Box 23, Folder 217)
    - Ohm, undated (Box 23, Folder 218)
    - One Year Performance, undated (Box 23, Folder 219)
    - Pangaea, undated (Box 23, Folder 220)
    - PaintingsDirect.com, undated (Box 23, Folder 221)
    - Pioneer Theater, undated (Box 23, Folder 222)
    - Philip Alan Gallery, undated (Box 23, Folder 223)
    - POPaganda, undated (Box 23, Folder 224)
    - P.P.O.W., undated (Box 23, Folder 225)
    - Present Co. Theatorium, undated (Box 23, Folder 226)
    - Printed Matter, Inc., undated (Box 23, Folder 227)
    - Public Theater, undated (Box 23, Folder 228)
    - REPOhistory, undated (Box 23, Folder 229)
    - Roger Smith Gallery, undated (Box 23, Folder 230)
    - Roxy, undated (Box 23, Folder 231)
    - Sakura Park, undated (Box 23, Folder 232)
    - Sam Cintron Gallery, undated (Box 23, Folder 233)
    - Sandra Gering Gallery, undated (Box 23, Folder 234)
    - Sideshow, undated (Box 23, Folder 235)
    - Simon Gallery, undated (Box 23, Folder 236)
    - Small Press Book Fair, undated (Box 23, Folder 237)
    - Spa, undated (Box 23, Folder 238)
    - Spectra Digital Arts Gallery, undated (Box 23, Folder 239)
    - Studio 18 Gallery, undated (Box 23, Folder 240)
    - Subculture, undated (Box 23, Folder 241)
    - System, undated (Box 23, Folder 242)
    - Thread Waxing Space, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Track 16 Gallery, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Total Theater Lab, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Tricia Collins Contemporary Art, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Twirl, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Upstate Art, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - USA, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - VIA Festival, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Weston, Frederick and Bruce Benderson, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Wetlands Preserve, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - WFMU Marathon, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Whitney Museum, undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Yaddo, undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Yankee Clipper, undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Zinsser, John, undated (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Accretions 2000-2001 - Series VII: Sound recordings
  also includes videorecordings
  - Algebra Suicide. The Secret Like Crazy. 1987-Compact Disk. (Box 30)
  - Algebra Suicide. Swoon. 1991-Compact Disk. (Box 30)
  - Algebra Suicide. Tongue Wrestling. 1994-Compact Disk. (Box 30)
  - Huberman, David, Catherine Sand, Susan Scutti at Parkside reading, 12/7/1998. Videotape. (Box 30)
  - Packer, Eve and Noah Howard. That Look. 2000-Compact Disk. (Box 30)
  - People's Poetry Gathering, 2001-Compact Disk. (Box 30)
  - Tomkiw, Lydia. Incorporated, 1995-Compact Disk. (Box 30)
- Accretions 2000-2001 - Series VIII: Original Art
  - Digital Art for Digitas, undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Restino, Janet, undated (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Shalom, undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Misc. drawings, undated (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Accretions 2000-2001 - Series IX: Ephemera
  Box 2 of Series IX - Ephemera
  - Two t-shirts designed by Junichi Tsunoda, with poetry by Sharon Mesmer, undated (Box 31)
  - One t-shirt entitled Broadshirt with poetry from Japanese avant-garde poets, undated (Box 31)
- Accretions 2000-2001 - Series XII: Catalogs
  - Anthology Film Archives, Jan.-Mar. 2001 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Anthology Film Archives, Apr.-Jun. 2001 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Anthology Film Archives, July-Sept. 2001 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Burning Deck Books, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - four walls eight windows, Fall 2000 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - four walls eight windows, Spring 2001 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Hanging Loose Press, 2000-01, 2000-2001 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Hanging Loose Press, 2001-02, 2001-2002 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Luzerner Comix-Festival, Mar. 30-Apr, 8, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Ram Publications and Distribution, 2000-01, 2000-2001 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Seven Stories Press, Spring/Summer 2000 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Seven Stories Press, Fall/Winter 2000 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Seven Stories Press, Spring-Summer 2001 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Small Press Distribution, Spring/Summer 2000 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Small Press Distribution, Fall/Winter 2000-01, 2000-2001 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Small Press Distribution, Spring/Summer 2001 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Thin Air Video, undated (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - U Turn, vol. 1, issue 2, Dec. 2000 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Verso, Spring 2000 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Verso, Autumn 2000 (Box 24, Folder 40)
- Accretions 2000-2001 - Oversize - Series XIII: Calendars
  Added to Oversize box 1 of Series 13
  - 1999 and 2000., 1999, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Accretions 2000-2001 - Series XIV: Periodicals
  - American Book Review: Vol. 21, no. 3, Mar.-Apr, 2000: Vol. 21, no. 4, May-Jun. 2000: Vol. 21, no. 5, Jul.-Aug. 2000 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - American Book Review: Vol. 22, no. 2, Jan-Feb. 2001: Vol. 22, no. 3, Mar.-Apr. 2001: Vol. 22, no. 4, May-Jun. 2001: Vol. 22, no. 5, Jul.-Aug. 2001 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - The Bridges In Our Lives: Writings by the Students of ASHS Castle Hill, undated (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Chess Life, May 2000 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Daily News Magazine, Apr. 22, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - The Eclectic, Vol. 2, no. 10, Mar. 2001 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Goldsmith, Kenneth. Index to the First Edition of Soliloquy., undated (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Hot, undated (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Juxtapoz, Vol. 5, no. 1, Spring 1998 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Lytle, Ellen Aug. from person to page July, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Medicinal Purposes, Vol. II, no. IV, Midyear, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - New Music Connoisseur, Vol. 9, no, 1, Spring, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - Phi Kappa Phi Journal, Vol. 81, no. 1, Winter, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - Poetry Project Newsletter, issue 185, Summer 2001 (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - Rain Taxi, Vol. 6, no. 2, Summer, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - Raven Chronicles, Vol. 10, no.1, undated (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - Simon, John F. Art Report 2001. (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - Spinning Jenny, no. 5, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - Spread the Poet, issue 6, Apr. 2001 (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - Underground Surrealist Magazine, issue 11, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 60)
  - Washington Free Press, no. 42, Nov.-Dec. 1999 (Box 24, Folder 61)
  - Williamsburg Observer, July 4, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 62)
  - Zwirn, issue 5, Summer 2000 (Box 24, Folder 63)
- Accretions 2002-2003 - Series I: Correspondence
  - Anthony, Bill, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Baldi, Malaga, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Basinski, Michael, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Curcio, Robert, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Davis, Heather, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Deyab, Larry, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Eidus, Janice, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Englendar, Stephen, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Fagin, Betsy, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Finberg, Bonny, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Hansen, Judith, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Hata, Takashi, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Hawa, Laura, undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Holder, Douglas, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Kupferberg, Tuli, undated (Box 25, Folder 14A)
  - MacPhee, Michael, undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Maurer, Susan, undated (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Morse, Elizabeth, undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Nodstrand, Judie, undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Nufer, Doug, undated (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Peabody, Richard, undated (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Plantenga, Bart, undated (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Ratner, Rochelle, undated (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Rosset, Barney, undated (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Seweryn, Natalie, undated (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Sirowitz, Hal, undated (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Solomon, Tanya, undated (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Theriopoulos, Georgette, undated (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Vallone, Peter F. Jr., undated (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Vitale, Alfred, undated (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - White, C., undated (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Wilson, Peter Lamborn, undated (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Witz, Bob, undated (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Wright, Jeff, undated (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Postits from multiple correspondents, undated (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Unidentified/Partial Name, undated (Box 25, Folder 35)
- Accretions 2002-2003 - Series II: Manuscripts
  - Basinski, Michael--Book Reviews, undated (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Blagg, Max--Hospital Food, undated (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Chomsky, Noam--9-11, undated (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Cory, Jean-Jacques--Academic Critics of the Avant-Garde, undated (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Dalachinsky, Steve--"A Free Lancing of Freelance", undated (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Dombrowski, Bob--The War Years, undated (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Feast, Jim (with Ron Kolm)--Afterword: Any Good Books…, undated (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Feast, Jim "AIDS: A Second Opinion", undated (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Feast, Jim (with Ron Kolm)--Freelance (Pitch), undated (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Feast, Jim (with Ron Kolm)--Freelance (Prelude), undated (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Feast, Jim (with Ron Kolm)--Freelance (Working MS 1/4), undated (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Feast, Jim (with Ron Kolm)--Freelance (Working MS 2/4), undated (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Feast, Jim (with Ron Kolm)--Freelance (Working MS 3/4), undated (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Feast, Jim (with Ron Kolm)--Freelance (Working MS 4/4), undated (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Feast, Jim (with Ron Kolm)-- Freelance 1/2, undated (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Feast, Jim (with Ron Kolm)-- Freelance 2/2, undated (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Feast, Jim (with Ron Kolm)-- Return to Sender: The Ed Zines Story (working MS), undated (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Feast, Jim (with Ron Kolm)-- Return to Sender: The Ed Zines Story, undated (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Feast, Jim--"Review of Steve Dalachinsky's A Superintendent's Eyes", undated (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - Feast, Jim (with Ron Kolm)--"Unbearable Portfolio Three, Theme Collaboration", undated (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - Feast, Jim --Untitled MS, undated (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - Feast, Jim --Draft of Untitled Novel, undated (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Huberman, David--Full Circle, undated (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Kolm, Ron--Westbeth Application, undated (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Kostelanetz, Richard--Essays, undated (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - Kupferburg, Tuli--Uranus, undated (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - Life, Kathy, undated (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - Nostrand, Judie--Poems, undated (Box 25, Folder 63)
  - Public Illumination Magazine [materials], undated (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - Nufer, Doug--Atlas Slugged, undated (Box 25, Folder 65)
  - Nufer, Doug, undated (Box 25, Folder 66)
  - Pritchard, A. A., undated (Box 25, Folder 67)
  - Rosset, Barney--Our Humanity is Still Here, undated (Box 25, Folder 68)
  - Rutkowski, Thaddeus--Sex-Fiend Monologues (MS and Proof), undated (Box 25, Folder 69)
  - Rutkowski, Thaddeus--White and Wong, undated (Box 25, Folder 70)
  - Savage, Tom, undated (Box 25, Folder 71)
  - Sparrow--Poem, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Sykes, Floyd--I'm Your Man 1/2, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Sykes, Floyd--I'm Your Man 2/2, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Tsongas, George [poems], undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Witz, Bob--"A Proposal", undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Zummer, Thomas--Some Notes on the Unspeakable, undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Accretions 2002-2003 - Series III: The Unbearables
  - Subseries A: The Unbearables
    - Help Yourself Reading, 5/23/1997 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Unbearables Portfolio #3, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Assembling Magazine #13 [materials], undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Assembling Magazine #13, 9/2001 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Assembling Magazine #14 [materials], undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Assembling Magazine #14, 10/28/2001 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Beatfest 2002 Flyer and Program, 4/12/2002 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Assembling Magazine #15 [materials], undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Assembling Magazine #15, 4/28/2002 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Colored White Women Artists [materials], undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Colored White Women Artists Catalogue, 5/04/2002 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Colored White Women Artists Flyers, 5/04/2002 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Unbearables Arts Festival Program [materials], undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Unbearables Arts Festival Program, 5/2002 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Unbearables Arts Festival Clippings, 5/2002 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Unbearables Arts Festival, undated (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Malcolm McLaren: Not for Sale, 8/27/2002 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - National Post Article, 8/30/2002 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - New York Sun Article, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Assembling Magazine #16 [materials], undated (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Assembling Magazine #16, 10/13/2002 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Help Yourself Readings, multiple dates (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Smithsonian Article, 11/2002 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Help Yourself Reading, 3/27/2003 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Call for entries: Life Café book, undated (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Drink Policy, undated (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Help Yourself Reading, undated (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Life-Time Non-Achievement Award Tuli Kupfenberg, undated (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - World's Longest Love Poem, undated (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Worst Book Reading, undated (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Subseries C: Help Yourself
    - Related Correspondence, undated (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Research Materials, undated (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Used and Unused Manuscripts (1/3), undated (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Used and Unused Manuscripts (2/3), undated (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Used and Unused Manuscripts (3/3), undated (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - 3 ¼ inch floppy discs IBM format, undated (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - 3 ¼ inch floppy discs IBM and Mac formats, undated (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Used and Unused Graphics, undated (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - Jim Feast forward and afterward MS, undated (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - Box Top/Checklist for First Typescript, undated (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - First Typescript (1/2), undated (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - First Typescript (2/2), undated (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - Second Typescript, undated (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - Cover Graphic, proof, undated (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - First Proof, undated (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - Corrected Proof (incomplete), undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Second Proof (1/2), undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Second Proof (2/2), undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Final Proof, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Accretions 2002-2003 - Series IV: Subject Files
  - Subseries A: Writers and Artists
    - Appearances Magazine, undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Anthony, William, undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Aronson, David, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Azon, Gary, undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Blagg, Max, undated (Box 27, Folder 9)